[
    {
        "front": "א",
        "back": "Alef"
    },
    {
        "front": "ב",
        "back": "Bet"
    },
    {
        "front": "ג",
        "back": "Gimel"
    },
    {
        "front": "ד",
        "back": "Dalet"
    },
    {
        "front": "ה",
        "back": "He"
    },
    {
        "front": "ו",
        "back": "Vav"
    },
    {
        "front": "ז",
        "back": "Zayin"
    },
    {
        "front": "ח",
        "back": "Het"
    },
    {
        "front": "ט",
        "back": "Tet"
    },
    {
        "front": "י",
        "back": "Yod"
    },
    {
        "front": "כ",
        "back": "Kaf"
    },
    {
        "front": "ך",
        "back": "Kaf"
    },
    {
        "front": "ל",
        "back": "Lamed"
    },
    {
        "front": "מ",
        "back": "Mem"
    },
    {
        "front": "ם",
        "back": "Mem"
    },
    {
        "front": "נ",
        "back": "Nun"
    },
    {
        "front": "ן",
        "back": "Nun"
    },
    {
        "front": "ס",
        "back": "Samekh"
    },
    {
        "front": "ע",
        "back": "Ayin"
    },
    {
        "front": "פ",
        "back": "Pe"
    },
    {
        "front": "ף",
        "back": "Pe"
    },
    {
        "front": "צ",
        "back": "Tsadi"
    },
    {
        "front": "ץ",
        "back": "Tsadi"
    },
    {
        "front": "ק",
        "back": "Qof"
    },
    {
        "front": "ר",
        "back": "Resh"
    },
    {
        "front": "ש",
        "back": "Shin"
    },
    {
        "front": "ת",
        "back": "Tav"
    }
]